It's Just Like Paradise, Only Better Looking.
Dinosaur Island is a adventure, comedy, fantasy film directed by Fred Olen Ray.
Welcome to lush Dinosaur Island, where a tribe of gorgeous cavedwelling warrior
women satisfy the exotic fantasies of five downed military airmen.
Fearsome battles with the island's ferocious maneating dinosaurs are the only
disruption of their seductive pleasures on this island paradise.
Narrowly surviving with their lives, the rugged men fall under the seductive spell
of their lovely captors and soon find their every dream fulfilled.
Capt. Jason Briggs, played by Ross Hagen.
John Skeemer, played by Richard Gabai.
April, played by Antonia Dorian.
May, played by Griffin Drew.
June, played by Michelle Bauer.
Turbo, played by Peter Spellos.
Dinosaur Island is a 1994 B-movie directed by Fred Olen Ray and Jim Wynorski.
Wynorski called it "a very 1950s type of picture, like The Lost Continent
except that we're going to have better dinosaurs and more girls."
The film explores themes of island, army, beach, prophecy, tyrannosaurus rex.
The tone is lighthearted.